Viewers, are you there?
Whatever medium you are using to view us at this moment,
just believe with God, all things are possible.
Viewers all over the world, are you still holding any pain of the past or unforgiveness?
Ask Jesus Christ to make you a channel of pardon where there is injury.
Ask Jesus to make you a channel of forgiveness where there is unforgiveness;
a channel of love where there is hatred,
in Jesus Christ's name, we pray.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Lord.
Now, it is time to move forward.
You can talk to Jesus.
Say, "I can talk to my Father".
Our Father in Heaven
We glorify Your Name
We bow down before You
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
I have come, oh Lord!
You said, "Come, all ye that labour and are oppressed".
I have come, oh Lord.
Deliver me, in the name of Jesus!
Deliver me, in the name of Jesus from that spirit that holds my health,
from that spirit that holds my marriage,
from that spirit that holds my family,
from that spirit that holds my finances,
from that spirit that holds my career,
from that spirit that holds my future.
Be delivered!
Prayer!
Begin to disconnect yourself!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, those who wait upon the Lord shall never be disappointed.
Whatever disease or sickness in your organs - never a sickness Jesus cannot cure.
Never a disease Jesus cannot heal.
Be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
When the Son forgives, you are forgiven.
When the Son forgives, you are delivered.
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Every pain in your kidneys, liver, blood, bones - wherever it is located -
I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Agree with me - you are delivered!
I can see you being delivered!
I can see you being healed!
I can see you being set free!
Rejoice!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Hallelujah!